<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Paul Hübner</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Paul Hübner</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© 2025 Paul Hübner</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 21:33:12 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Functional Programming</title>
      <link>/posts/state/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 21:33:12 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/state/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the earliest frustrations I encountered in programming was that I had to re-do stuff I had already done before, maybe 6-12 months after first starting.
Often writing similar code that was just about different enough to make copy/paste or reuse tricky is not fun, especially when the novelty factor is gone.
Not to mention all the Java boilerplate&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Candor: A Simple and Powerful CI Ecosystem</title>
      <link>/posts/candor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 17:11:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/candor/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Candor is a CI ecosystem - a dashboard with runners - that not only caters to my needs but is also a manifestation of what happens when I let my passion
and perfectionism get the better of me.
Behind it is a multi-year process, months of active development, fuelled by caffeine and sheer commitment.
If you would like to check it out, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Arraying/Candor&#34;&gt;you can view the project on GitHub&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building the Best Anti-Fraud Bot You&#39;ve Never Heard Of</title>
      <link>/posts/antifraud/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 18:30:54 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/antifraud/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I made a Discord bot that will automatically detect fraudulent Steam/Nitro links on Discord, and ban the person sending these.
The impressive part: it works on never-before seen links, and its false-positive and false-negative rate is &lt;em&gt;ridiculously&lt;/em&gt; low.
It&amp;rsquo;s totally open source and you can protect your server too!
Check out the &lt;a href=&#34;#installation&#34;&gt;Installation&lt;/a&gt; section if you are interested.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
